A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Near & Middle East, Record Group 3, Series 9 FA1777
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on the Near and Middle East, 1959-1996; 1; 26.06 Cubic Feet 66 containers
  - Langerman, Yitzhak - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 639)
  - Khoury, Dina - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 640)
  - Loeffler-Friedl, Erika - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 641)
  - Hill, Enid - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 642)
  - Phillips, Beth - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1990 - Predoctoral Award (Box 65, Folder 643)
  - Rieker, Martina - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1989 - Predoctoral Award, 1990-1992 (Box 65, Folder 644)
  - Sayari, Sabri - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1990 (Box 66, Folder 645)
  - Hill, Enid - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant Reports, 1990-1996 (Box 66, Folder 646)
  - Near and Middle East Research Fellowships Transcripts, 1988-1993 (Box 77, Folder 789)
  - Workshop: State Creation and Transformation - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 647)
  - Istanbul Committee Meeting, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 648)
  - Retreating States and Expanding Societies: The State Autonomy/Informal Civil Society Dialectic in the Middle East and North Africa, 1985-1987 (Box 66, Folder 649-650)
  - Budget, 1984-1987 (Box 66, Folder 651)
  - Reports to Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 652)
  - Hierarchy and Stratification in the Contemporary Near and Middle East Volume - Release Letters, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 653)
  - Hierarchy and Stratification in the Contemporary Near and Middle East - Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 66, Folder 654, Box 67, Folder 655)
  - Ibn Khaldun Prize Declinations, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 656-659)
  - International Doctoral Research Fellowship - Overseas Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 660)
  - Near and Middle East Predoctoral Screening Note Sheets, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 661)
  - Near and Middle East Postdoctoral Screening Note Sheets and Master Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 662)
  - Policies and Procedures for Western Europe - International Doctoral Research Fellowship Program, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 663)
  - Award Selection Committee, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 664)
  - Spring Meeting - March 1989, 1987-1989 (Box 68, Folder 665-666)
  - Middle East Studies Association (MESA), 1984-1988 (Box 68, Folder 667)
  - Fellowship Award Letters, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 668)
  - Ranking Sheets for Applicants, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 669)
  - International Research Fellowships and Grants for Advanced Research Policies and Procedures Manual and Rankings, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 670)
  - Near and Middle East 1988-1989 Fellowship Letters, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 671)
  - Middle East Studies Association - 1989 Meeting (Box 69, Folder 672)
  - Committee Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 673)
  - Statistical Reports - Predoctoral Dissertation Fellowships and Postdoctoral Advanced Research Grants, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 674)
  - Postdoctoral Grants for Advanced Research, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 675)
  - Middle East Studies Association (MESA), 1990 (Box 69, Folder 676-677)
  - Ibn Khaldun Prize 1990 Papers, 1988-1991 (Box 69, Folder 678)
  - Aksan, Virginia - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 679)
  - Beinin, Joel - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 680)
  - Bianchi, Robert - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 681)
  - Chyet, Michael - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 682)
  - Eisenberg, Laura - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1992 (Box 69, Folder 683)
  - Frangakis-Syrett, Elena - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 684)
  - Hinnebush, Raymond - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1989-1991 (Box 69, Folder 685)
  - Dowty, Alan - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 686)
  - Escribano, Marisa - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 687)
  - Lourie, Kevin - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 688)
  - Messier, Donald - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 689)
  - Pourgerami, Abbas - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 690)
  - Schott, Thomas - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 691)
  - Schick, Robert - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 692)
  - Kasaba, Resat - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 693)
  - Shepard, William - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 694)
  - Swearingen, Will - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 695)
  - Tress, Madeleine - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 696)
  - Heath, Jeffrey - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 697)
  - Kuran, Timur - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 698)
  - Lewis, James - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 699)
  - Maschler, Yael - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 700)
  - Patton, Marcie - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 701)
  - Zohreh, Sullivan - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 702)
  - Ward, Seth - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 703)
  - Zuhur, Sherifa - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 704)
  - Denny, Walter - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant - Postdoctoral Declination, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 705)
  - Conference on Hierarchy and Stratification in the Contemporary Near and Middle East Volume - Folder A, 1979-1981 (Box 70, Folder 706-707)
  - Conference on Hierarchy and Stratification in the Contemporary Near and Middle East Volume - Folder B - Earlier Versions, 1979-1980 (Box 71, Folder 708)
  - Sub-Committee on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East - Robert Lapham Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 709)
  - Members of Tunisian Government, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 710)
  - Recruitment of New Committee Members, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 711)
  - Conference on Hierarchy and Stratification in the Contemporary Near and Middle East Papers, 1979-1983 (Box 71, Folder 712-725, Box 72, Folder 726-727)
    Folder 712 - State, Society, and Military Elites in the Middle East, Gabriel Ben-Dor
    Folder 713 - Marxist and Weberian Intellectual Traditions and the Social Structures of the Middle East, Abdelkader Zghal
    Folder 714 - Overgrown Bureaucracy and National Community: Egypt Compared with Other Arab States, Clement Henry Moore
    Folder 715 - Abortive Class Conflict: The Failure of Peasant Uprisings in 19th Century Lebanon, Samir Khalaf
    Folder 716 - State and the Economy in Modern Turkey, Caglar Keyder
    Folder 717 - Class Analysis and Iraqi Society, Hanna Batatu
    Folder 718 - Marxist and Weberian Intellectual Traditions and the Social Structures of the Middle East, Abdelkader Zghal
    Folder 719 - On the Institutionalization of Privilege in the Middle East, Serif Mardin; "Traditional" Concepts of Social Hierarchy, Bulliet; Stratification and Group Conciousness, Marvin Zonis; Abortive Class Conflict: The Failure of Peasant Uprisings in Nineteenth Century Lebanon, Samir Khalaf; Class Analysis and Iraqi Society, Hanna Batatu
    Folder 720 - State, Society, and Military Elites in the Middle East, Gabriel Ben-Dor; Marxist and Weberian Intellectual Traditions and the Social Structures of the Middle East, Abdelkader Zghal
    Folder 721 - The 'Ulama' as Officials and as Popular Leaders, Nehemia Levtzion
    Folder 722 - State, Society, and Military Elites in the Middle East, Gabriel Ben-Dor
    Folder 723 - State and Economy in Modern Turkey, Caglar Keyder
    Folder 724 - On the Institutionalization of Privilege in the Middle East, Serif Mardin
    Folder 725 - Group Conciousness, Hierarchy, and Stratification in the Iranian Revolution, Marvin Zonis
    Folder 726 - State and Economy in Modern Turkey, Caglar Keyder
    Folder 727 - State and Economy in Modern Turkey, Caglar Keyder
  - Conference on Hierarchy and Stratification in the Contemporary Near and Middle East Papers - Correspondence and Notes, 1981-1983 (Box 72, Folder 728-729)
  - Conference on Hierarchy and Stratification in the Contemporary Near and Middle East Volume, 1979-1982 (Box 72, Folder 730-731)
  - Spring 1988 Meeting Agenda (Box 72, Folder 732)
  - Meeting Proposals, Notes, and Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 72, Folder 733)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 734)
  - Fall 1987 Meeting (Box 72, Folder 735)
  - Fall 1986 Meeting, Coto de Caza, California (Box 73, Folder 736)
  - Fall 1987 Meeting Agenda (Box 73, Folder 737)
  - Fall 1986 Meeting Agenda (Box 73, Folder 738)
  - Spring 1986 Meeting (Box 73, Folder 739)
  - Ibn Khaldun Prize Papers, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 740-743)
  - Papers and Memos for Fall 1986 Meeting (Box 74, Folder 744-745)
  - The Informal Sector of the Economy in the Middle East and in North Africa: Issues and Objectives for a Proposed Conference, Peter von Sivers, 1983-1984 (Box 74, Folder 746)
  - The Informal Sector of the Economy in Selected Countries of the Third World International Conference, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 747)
  - The State, Religion, and Ethnic Politics Volume and Conference Correspondence, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 748)
  - The Informal Sector of the Economy in Selected Countries of the Third World International Conference, Tutzing, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 749)
  - The Ottoman Empire and World Capitalism Conference, State University of New York at Binghampton, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 750)
  - Property, Social Structure, and Law in the Modern Middle East, Edited by Ann Elizabeth Mayer, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 751)
  - Ibn Khaldun Prize Graduate Student Paper Competition Papers and Conference Papers, 1987-1988 (Box 74, Folder 752-753, Box 75, Folder 754)
  - State Formation and Nation-Building in Arab Oil-Producing Countries Conference Finances, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 755)
  - The Political Economy of Oil Production in the Middle East - Project Reports, 1982-1984 (Box 75, Folder 756)
  - The Political Economy of Oil Production in the Middle East - Research Planning, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 757)
  - Social Change in Arab Oil-Producing Countries - Project Correspondence, Eric Davis, 1982-1985 (Box 75, Folder 758)
  - Social Change in Arab Oil-Producing Countries - Correspondence - Peter Gran, Samira Haj, and Rifaat Abou El-Haj, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 759)
  - Proposal for the Creation of a Research Seminar on Oil Wealth and State Formation in the Oil-Producing Countries of the Arab World, Latin America, and West Africa, Eric Davis, Robert R. Kaufman, Georg Elwert - National Endowment for the Humanities Proposal, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 760)
  - Task Force - Social Change in Arab Oil-Producing Countries - Report and Invitation Letters, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 761)
  - Social Change in Arab Oil-Producing Countries Proposal Submitted to The Symposia Program of Stiftung Volkswagenwerk, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 762)
  - Core Project - A Case for Culture, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 763)
  - Social Stratification in the Middle East and North Africa - Volume, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 764)
  - The Informal Sector of the Economy in the Middle East and in North Africa Proposal, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 765)
  - The State of the Field of Near and Middle Eastern Studies, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 766)
  - Project on Urban Women in Cairo, Fifi Marsot, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 767)
  - Institute of International Studies - Social Legislation in the Middle East Volume, 1983-1987 (Box 75, Folder 768)
  - Condolence Letters for Robert Lapham, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 769)
  - Family, Law, and Change in the Middle East Conference Write-Up for Items, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 770)
  - Cultural Change in the Mediterranean World and the Near East in Late Antiquity Seminar, Stephen Humphreys, 1981-1984 (Box 75, Folder 771)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure of the Joint Committee on the Near and Middle East, 1980-1984 (Box 75, Folder 772)
  - From Nationalism to Revolutionary Islam, Edited by Said Arjomand, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 773)
  - Task Force on Stratification in the Middle East, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 774)
  - Deniz Kandiyoti Papers, 1987-1989 (Box 76, Folder 775)
  - Judith Tucker Papers, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 776)
  - Spring 1986 Meeting - New York City (Box 76, Folder 777)
  - Fall 1985 Meeting - Berlin (Box 76, Folder 778)
  - August 1984 Meeting - Morocco (Box 76, Folder 779)
  - Meeting Agenda, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 780)
  - Fall 1984 Meeting, 1984 February (Box 76, Folder 781)
  - Future Committee Members, 1986-1987 (Box 76, Folder 782)
  - Khoury, Dina - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant 1991 - Postdoctoral Award, 1990-1992 (Box 78, Folder 791)
  - Goldberg, Ellis - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant 1990 - Postdoctoral Award (Box 78, Folder 792)
  - Mundy, Martha - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant 1990 - Postdoctoral Award, 1989-1991 (Box 78, Folder 793)
  - Swedenburg, Theodore - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant 1990 - Postdoctoral Award (Box 78, Folder 794)
  - Abdullah, Thabit - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1989 - Predoctoral Award, 1988-1991 (Box 78, Folder 795)
  - Graduate Student Paper Competition - Student Certifications, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 796)
    Notes from professors indicating the competition candidates are students
  - Beck, Lois - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant 1989 - Grant Extension - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1991 (Box 78, Folder 797)
  - Meeker, Michael - Near and Middle East Advanced Area Research Grant 1990, 1991 - Postdoctoral Award (Box 78, Folder 798)
- Joint Committee on the Comparative Study of Muslim Societies, 1984-1995; 2; 6.93 Cubic Feet 17 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
  From 1985-1993, the Joint Committee for the Comparative Study of Muslim Societies was active in encouraging interdisciplinary research into the relationship between Islamic systems of faith and knowledge in the social lives of Muslims. The basic mandate of the Committee was to help clarify the content, context, and linkages of Muslim nations and communities around the world. The Committee held dissertation workshops for graduate students, conducted a postdoctoral training and research grants program, and published books, including "Islam and the Political Economy of Meaning," "Muslim Travelers," and "Intellectuals and Militants." The Committee also focused on research projects such as "Movement and Change in Muslim Societies," "Being Muslim in a Non-Muslim Society," "Intellectuals and Militants in the Contemporary Muslim World," "The Making of a Fatwa," "Muslim Transnationalism," "Muslim Travelers," and "Vernacular Texts and Local Knowledge of Islam." The Ford Foundation provided the bulk of the funding for the committee with two grants beginning in 1985. The Committee was a joint committee of the Social Science Research Council and the American Council of Learned Societies. The Social Science Research Council itself is not a foundation, although it possesses a small sustaining fund. It does not depend on an endowment for its income, as do foundations; rather, it is a claimant agency to foundations for grants which have terms of one to five years.
  The Joint Committee for the Comparative Study of Muslim Societies subseries contains administrative correspondence related to organizing meetings, recruiting members, and obtaining grants, conference proposals and planning materials, research proposals, dissertation workshop invitations, and committee budgets.
  - Key Documents, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Muslim Chronological Correspondence File A-Z, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 49-51)
  - David Szanton Chronological Correspondence File A-Z, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 52-54)
  - David Szanton Chronological Correspondence File A-Z, 1988 April-1989 December (Box 8, Folder 55-57)
  - Social Science Research Council, International Conference on the Making of Fatwa, Granada, Spain, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 58-59)
  - Making Space for Islam: Special Expressions Muslims in the West, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 60-61)
  - On Being Muslim in Non-Muslim Countries, Paris and Delhi, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 62, Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Comparative Muslim Studies Movement & Exchange I and II Unpublished Papers and Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Social Science Research Council Items, Volume 43, Numbers 1 and 4, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Joint Committee on Comparative Study of Muslim Societies - New Proposal - Drafts, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Joint Committee on Comparative Study of Muslim Societies - Proposal.doc, 1991; 5.25" floppy disk (Box 15)
  - Workshop on Colonial and Post-Colonial Constructions of Communal Identity, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Spatial Expressions of Muslim Identity in the West Conference, November 1-4, 1990, 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 124-125)
  - Spatial Expressions of Muslim Identity in the West Conference - Budget, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Workshop on Vernacular Texts and Local Knowledge of Islam, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Workshop on Vernacular Texts and Local Knowledge of Islam - Responses, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Transnational Da'wa Workshop, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Expenses - Granada - The Making of Fatwa, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Granada Conference, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 131-132)
  - General Committee Material, 1990 January-April (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - Cairo Dissertation Workshop (Originally Yemen), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 134-135, Box 17, Folder 136)
  - Committee Correspondence and Project Proposals, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Committee Meeting, New York City, 1988 September (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Committee Membership Lists and Meeting Materials, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Kelantan, Malaysia Dissertation Workshop, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Committee Correspondence and Project Proposals, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - William Roff Correspondence, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - Committee Planning Correspondence and April 1991 Meeting Agenda (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - Committee Planning Correspondence, Proposals, and Budget Materials, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Committee Member Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 145, Box 18, Folder 146-147)
  - June 1990 Meeting Budget (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - Administrative Materials and Committee Project Proposals, 1985-1995 (Box 30, Folder 246-250)
  - Lila Abu-Lughod's Proposal Draft - The Popular Appeal of Islam: The 1990s, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 251)
  - Memo - Request for Seed Funding for Working Group on Central and Inner Asia, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 252)
  - Ford Foundation Grant - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 30, Folder 253)
  - Potential Sources of Funding - Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 254)
  - Problems and Policy Oversight Committee - Proposal Drafts - The Popular Appeal of Islam: The 1990s, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 255)
  - Transnational Da'wa Workshop Planning, Wales, 1992 April (Box 30, Folder 256)
  - Committee Membership Lists, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 267)
  - Draft Renewal Proposal - Program Discussion Paper Prepared for the International Affairs Program of the Ford Foundation, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 268, Box 31, Folder 269)
  - R. B. Oakley CSIS (Center for Strategic and International Studies?) Speech, 1991 September 20 (Box 31, Folder 270)
  - Lila Abu Lughod's Version/Revised Proposal - The Popular Appeal of Islam: The 1990s, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 271)
  - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 272)
  - The Making of a Fatwa Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 273)
  - Muslims Under Non-Muslim Rule Conference, 1987 December (Box 49, Folder 470)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Applications, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 471)
  - Dissertation Workshop, 1986 April (Box 50, Folder 472)
  - Research Grant Applications, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 473)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Tangier, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 474-475)
  - Fatwa Workshop - Original Abstracts, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 476)
  - Committee Correspondence, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 477)
  - Postdoctoral Grant Declinations, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 478)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Mark Saroyan, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 479)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Sabiha Khemir, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 480)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Jamal Elias, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 481)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Albrecht Hofheinz, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 482)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Tazim Kassam, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 483)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Latifa Laghzaoui, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 484)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Catherine Mayeur, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 485)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Jalil Miswardi, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 486)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Francis Mullaney, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 487)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Delphine Roger, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 488)
  - Dissertation Workshop - June Santosa, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 489)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Leonardo Villaln, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 490)
  - Dissertation Workshop Declinations, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 491-492)
  - Movement and Exchange Workshop I (Muslim Travelers), 1985-1989 (Box 52, Folder 493-494)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Kelantan, Malaysia, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 495)
  - Dissertation Declinations, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 496)
  - Dissertation Workshop - James Gelvin, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 497)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Richard McGrail, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 498)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Allyson Purpura, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 499)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Stuart Sears, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 500)
  - Mailing Lists, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 501)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Neguin Yavari, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 502)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Jane Drakard, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 503)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Daniel Brown, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 504)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Jamsheed Choksy, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 505)
  - Dissertation Workshop - JoAnn D'Alisera, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 506)
  - Dissertation Workshop - John Dixon, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 507)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Patricia Horavitch, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 508)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Jeff Romero, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 509)
  - Materials for Dissertation Workshop: Committee Biographies, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 510)
  - 1991 Workshop Invitation - Barbara Metcalf, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 511)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Deborah Amory, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 512)